thedailymash.co.uk 2019-12-22

# The Daily Mash | Privacy policy and settings

Hello. We’ve updated our privacy policy for this new GDPR thing, not that you care in the slightest. Like every site out there we at thedailymash.co.uk collect some information online which we use to develop and enhance the services we offer to you. This involves the use of cookies. Cookies are not inherently evil, in fact their use in advertising is one of the main reasons you are able to read this for free.

**The Short Version**

This privacy statement is the privacy notice for all Daily Mash services. We will use your details to provide you with the service which you or someone else (with your CONSENT) have asked us to provide.

**Your privacy settings and right to withdraw consent**

When you first visit our site you will be asked to set your consent preferences and determine how you want your data to be used. You may set your preferences for us independently from those of third-party partners. Each purpose has a description so that you know how we and partners use your data. You can change your own personal cookie settings and withdraw consent anytime you want to by clicking HERE.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small files of letters and numbers. These files are either stored in the memory of your computer or other device such as mobile phones or tablet devices (these cookies are generally known as session cookies) or are placed on the hard drive of your device (generally known as persistent cookies).  
Cookies are created when you visit a website or other service that uses cookies. We and our partners use cookies to make content, services and advertising more relevant and useful during future visits.

We use functional cookies to help provide our services, so for example:  
● by limiting the number of times that any adverts which you view on our services are repeated within a short space of time.

We use analytical cookies to review and analyse user interactivity with our services, including in relation to content and advertising. For example, we may use analytical cookies to:

● recognise and to count the number of visitors to our services;  
● to see how you and other users move around within our services and to record which content viewers view; or  
● determine when advertising has been served and to which users.

If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you read on or visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/ "About cookies") or [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/ "Your Online Choices"). Deleting cookies may impair the functionality of this site and your enjoyment of it.

We take privacy issues seriously and are open about the way data is collected and used. Please read this policy which outlines the principles we follow.

We are committed to:  
– protecting the personal information you give us  
– telling you how we use the information we gather from you  
– getting your consent to our disclosure of your personal information

**More on cookies**

We use a number of different cookies on our site. For example:

**Google Analytics –  **we use this to understand how the site is being used in order to improve the user experience. User data is all anonymous. You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at [http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html](https://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

Quantcast – this cookie captures information on site traffic and usage so we can better understand our audience. User data is all anonymous.

Switch Concepts – this cookie is used to deliver & monitor performance of the display adverts on our site. User data is all anonymous.  See here for more info: <http://www.switchconcepts.com/privacy.html>

To opt out of any of these services go to:

GOOGLE ANALYTICS  
QUANTCAST  
<https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out>  
SWITCH CONCEPTS  
<http://www.switchconcepts.com/privacy.html>

Through the use of cookies, anonymous information about your use of our websites and other websites will be used to provide more relevant adverts about goods and services of interest to you. For more information on online behavioural advertising and about how to turn this feature off, please visit <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk>

**We are committed to protecting your privacy.  
**We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service and only after you have given consent via our consent tools. This Policy indicates the type of processes that may result in data being collected about you.

**Information Collected**  
We may collect any or all of the information that you give us depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including your name, address, telephone number, and email address, together with data about your use of the website. Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website.

**Information Use**  
We use the information collected primarily to help us improve our site to make it enjoyable for you to visit. Data collected in the UK is held in accordance with the Data Protection Act. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorised access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details.

**Information storage**

We keep your personal data for only as long as we need to. How long we need you personal data depends on what we are using it for, as set out in this privacy policy. For example, we may need to keep your personal data for accounting purposes where you have bought a subscription.

**Disclosing Information**  
We do not disclose any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties unless you permit us to do so by ticking the relevant boxes in registration or competition forms. We may also use the information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with us. You will be given the opportunity to remove yourself from any mailing list or similar device. If at any time in the future we should wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it would only be with your knowledge and consent.

We may from time to time provide information of a general nature to third parties – for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or completing a registration form, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals.

**Contacting Us**

If you have questions or wish to submit a Data Access request, please email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or write to Publisher, Digitalbox Publishing Limited, 2-4 Henry Street, Bath, BA1 1JT and we will respond as soon as possible. We may need to establish proof of your identity before we provide information. You can also correct any factual errors in that information or require us to remove your details form any list under our control.

**How to complain**

If you wish to complain you should contact the supervisory body in the UK which is the Information Commissioners Office. The ICO is the UK’s independent authority set up to uphold information rights in the public interest, and data privacy for individuals. It can be contacted here: <https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/>
